United will call heads is a call
heads.
You will bowl first. Okay. I wish you
all the best. So three match last match
of day one. Gagaran added won the toss.
Elected to field first, bowling first.
And yes, gel
because
Sunday special.
This is the last match of day one.
Unilite strikers batters a set up the
field quickly. Galroed
Hello and welcome back once again. ICIC
Lombard presents proudly presents ICICI
Lombard probably presents Brokers
Premier League
season 3 2026.
Here
we go. Game on.
First ball striking really well for four
runs. Madok Kadam and Doddan
Wenesh Taudari
started the proceedings.
It's very good bowling from Wangadesh
trying to get that switched shot
uni strikers.
P gain thus run
boundary from Madokam.
One was gone. 11 for no loss. Unilite
strikers. You're watching this live from
Fatima grounds
and this is the last match of day one
but tomorrow we'll resume around 8:30
a.m. 9 a.m.
live from go live channel. So press the
bell icon and subscribe to get that
update once the stream started. So
you'll get auto notified. So subscribe
and press the bell icon to get the
updates of uh the day two. You'll get
auto notified on your mobile, on your
laptop,
on your iPad.
So, one was gone, 11 for no loss.
That's a good strike. Oh, that's taken.
Good catch taken.
Sir, catch taken by
12 for one after 1.1. That's one for
wide.
That's a good strike. We'll go for two
runs.
Is it out or two runs?
That's run out.
And that's a good strike
that will go all the way for four runs.
1.37 for two
two Unilite strikers
Kithan Guro to Mahetti
just going outside the off line for wide
Once again, back-to- back wides.
No ball signal by the umpire.
And we'll get one more run. That's one
run gift in the overthrows. No ball in
coming up. Free hit. Two extras
added to the total. 21 for two. Free hit
ball coming up. Rahul Bahiti on strike.
That was outside edge
and keeper
not able to stop that ball will get a
single run. 22 for2 after 1.4 the three
overs game and a much win for both the
teams.
Oh, he's dropped that.
We are already team AON qualified in the
quarterfinal and let's see the team who
wins from uh Unilite Strikers and Galaga
United will enter into qualifying round.
Just a single looking for two and mix
up. And this is a simple run out.
Suicidal run out.
That's a wicked fall number Three.
was going 24 for three. Unilite strikers
and coming to the last of the first
innings.
Let's see United strikers they will get
maximum runs there. They can get it and
wide plus one run
there. Two runs coming extra 26 for
three
strikers.
Tough fight
male.
Bes
wicket.
>> 28 for three.
Still have five six balls to go.
Four runs. They got extras.
That's a good strike. High in the air.
>> And they'll go for two.
30 for three.
Last five balls coming up.
And wow, high in the air. Chance
and dropped
two runs more.
32 for three.
Last four balls coming up. 32 for three.
Short backward
running.
Jordis
going down the leg for wide 35 for
three. Last three balls, 11 runs of the
over.
35 for three.
United
over Satis. Spectras.
That will count as one by. Let's see.
No, that came from the bat. Oh, they're
going for that one more run. What is
happening here?
and that's good placement and single
blowing for two runs.
And that will be the end of the first
innings.
So after three overs
39 for five and 40 the target to chase
the team who wins will qualify in the
quarterfinals. A much win for both the
teams
Galaga United or Unilite Striker. Stay
tuned for the live action. This is the
last match of the day one and uh now
second inning
42 chase for Gala United.
AON team already qualified into the
qualifier qualifying round
quarterfinals.
Welcome back once again. 40 runs to
chase for Gallagher United. Arjun Sharma
on strike. Saga on non-strike. Mahhati
will start. Not easy to chase. 40 runs
in three overs. This is the last match
of the day one live from Fatima grounds.
You're watching this live from YouTube
channel of go live.
And starting with a good bowling went
for ball.
They need a one good over
at least as five runs. They can easily
defend this total of 39.
Moetti
that's a good strike.
Bit uh slloppy in the field a bit of
because of the due factor but still uh
very good stop by the field only single
Very
good stop at the backward region.
Three balls, two runs, no wicket. 38
runs in 15 balls.
It's a bit of tough to chase for
Gallagher Gallagher United. But let's
see what Arjun Sharma and Saga will do
something special.
That's a good strike into the gaps. That
will run away for four runs. Yes, four
runs.
14 balls.
that went for ball. Five balls, six for
no loss. Good from my
two runs taken.
So one was gone, eight for no loss. They
need 32 runs in 12 balls.
Back to back. Two wickets and that will
go for four runs.
That's a good strike. Big one. It was
catch in the air in the com box for me.
That's a good strike for six runs. 22
for2. The target is 41.
This is something to be cheer for
Sanjiv. Sanjay.
And that will go for four more.
>> Excellent shot. Back to back boundaries.
What a match this is. What a match.
Excellent. Uh
batting, bowling,
very close.
Three ball 14 runs.
What a hatch.
Three ball 14.
Saga has got one six
and will be interesting to watch.
Need that one big hit for sure. Rahul
Bahiti 10 runs given in first three
balls
and 14 runs in coming three ball now.
Needed one dot ball.
Oh, THAT'S A GOOD STRIKE. WHAT YOU
BELIEVE IT? WOW.
SIX RUNS. WHAT A STRIKE FROM Sag Moar.
Sager Mosam
Kadakatch
>> [laughter]
>> Crazy moment.
to
sat 1426.
Here we go.
[screaming]
Super.
Last ball.
Super over.
Wow.
What a match. Give me a breather.
Wow. Fantastic performance. Seven runs,
one ball, one six goal level and we'll
be super over.
Here we go. Rahul Chagar.
And with that, that's a victory.
Unilight Strikers take a bow for Rahul
Bahetti.
They claim the victory. Unilites
strikers won by six runs
entering into the quarterfinals.
The team Aon in the quarterfinals and
now it was a biggest clash of titans
ended. Unilite strikers won by six runs
qualified in the quarterfinals.
So that's the end of the day one. We had
a fantastic day of ICS Lombard.